{"quizName":"ERP Chapter 4","questions":[{"question":"Which of the following statements about the goods receipt step are NOT true?","options":["It results in a decrease in inventory. ","It can occur during the procurement process.","It can result in the creation of material and financial accounting documents. ","Materials are placed in an appropriate storage location with an appropriate status. ","It can occur during the production process."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The key organizational level associated with inventory management is ","options":["Plant. ","Company code. ","Storage section. ","Storage area.","Storage location."],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"When do unplanned receipts occur? ","options":["When an invoice has been canceled","When material is transferred to another location","When a reference document does not exist","When a stock transfer is created","When the capacity of a storage location is exceeded"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"In the production process, a goods issue reflects","options":["Moving raw materials or semi-finished goods from a work center to storage bins.","Shipping finished goods or trading goods to a customer to fill a sales order.","Issuing finished goods to a production order. ","Shipping finished goods to a customer against a goods issue request.","Issuing raw materials or semi-finished goods to a production order."],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following scenarios requires material-to-material posting?","options":["Changing the material status from consignment to warehouse stock","Changing the material number of a material","Changing the material�s storage location","Changing the status of materials in stock","Changing the type of materials in stock"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which one of the following is NOT an example of using transfer postings?","options":["Changing the material status from consignment to warehouse stock","Changing the material number of a material","Changing the material�s storage location","Changing the status of materials in stock","Changing the type of materials in stock"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"What is a stock transfer used for?","options":["To change the status or type of materials in stock ","To show material movements when a material is received in the warehouse from the vendor�s location ","To indicate that a material-to-material change has been posted","To physically move materials from a storage location to the client�s warehouse","To physically move materials within the enterprise from one organizational level or location to another"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"Which of the following options is appropriate when two locations are physically close to each other and there is no significant time lag between issue and receipt?","options":["One-step procedure","Two-step procedure","Three-step procedure","Stock transport order","None of the above"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"A storage location-to-storage location transfer involves which of the following? ","options":["A stock transfer among several storage locations of two plants","A stock transfer between two storage locations of two plants","A stock transfer among several storage locations within the same plant","A stock transfer between two storage locations within the same plant ","A stock transfer between or among at least two storage locations within one or more plants"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"In plant-to-plant transfer, an FI document","options":["Is created in both one-step and two-step movements.","Is created in two-step movements only.","Is created in one-step movements only.","Is not created. "],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Which of the following represents the hierarchy of a warehouse?","options":["Warehouse, storage section, storage type, storage bin  ","Warehouse, storage bin, storage section, storage type","Warehouse, storage type, storage section, storage bin","Warehouse, storage section, storage bin, storage type","Warehouse, storage type, storage bin, storage section"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Shelf storage, pallet storage, and rack storage are examples of ","options":["Storage bins. ","Warehouses.","Storage sections.","Storage types.","None of the above"],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"A storage type is a division of a warehouse based on the characteristics of the ","options":["Weight, width, and type","Dimensions and profitability.","Space, materials, and activity.","Price, space, and type.","Usage, price, and dimensions."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"Fast-moving, slow-moving, heavy, light, large, and small are examples of ","options":["Storage bins. ","Warehouses.","Storage sections.","Storage types.","None of the above."],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"A picking area groups which of the following elements? ","options":["Shelves and pallets","Storage bins, based on similar picking strategies","Materials with similar transportation type","Materials with similar usage","Materials of the same material type"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"If a company stores a material in a storage location that is associated with a warehouse, then it must include additional data ","options":["In the storage location stock view of the material master for that material.","In the basic data view of the material master for that material.","In the general plant data/storage view of the material master for that material.","In the warehouse management view of the material master for that material.","No data need to be added. "],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Shelves, stacks, and aisles are examples of ","options":["Storage locations.","Coordinate systems for addresses.","Storage sections.","Storage identifiers.","Storage areas."],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following represents the document used to plan the movement of materials into and out of bins in a warehouse? ","options":["Transfer list","Transfer request","Transfer plan","Transfer order","Transfer requirement"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"Which of the following is a request to change the status of the material? ","options":["Posting change notice","Notice for change","Material change list","Status request list","Change request"],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"When creating a transfer order, you find that a particular material has to be moved from multiple source bins. Which of the following statements follows from this scenario?","options":["The transfer order will have multiple line items for the material.","More than one transfer order needs to be created.","The material will be written in one line item.","An internal order request will be created to move the material into one source bin.","This scenario is impossible."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"The ERP system can create transfer orders automatically, but only when ","options":["A destination is known.","The reference document is a transfer requirement   ","A warehouse movement type is specified.","A reference document exists.","Both the plant and the storage location are known."],"answerIndex":3},{"question":"Which of the following represents a possible sequence of steps in the warehouse movement process? ","options":["Create a transfer request, physically move the materials, confirm the movement, retrieve the transfer request","Physically move the materials, confirm the movement, create a transfer request, retrieve the transfer request","Physically move the materials, generate a transfer order, confirm the movement, retrieve the transfer order","Generate a transfer order, retrieve the transfer order. confirm the movement, physically  move the materials","Generate a transfer order, physically move the materials, retrieve the transfer order, confirm the movement"],"answerIndex":4},{"question":"In warehouse management steps associated with the procurement process, the warehouse inventory is calculated as sum of the inventory in the following places: ","options":["Storage sections and storage areas","Warehouse bins and storage sections","Interim storage areas and warehouse bins","Storage locations and storage sections","Storage locations and storage areas"],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"In a stock transfer from a plant where the storage location is warehouse managed to a plant where it is not, which of the following activities occurs at the receiving plant? ","options":["A goods receipt triggers WM process steps.","A simple goods receipt is recorded in IM.","A goods issue triggers WM process steps.","A simple goods issue is recorded in IM. ","None of the above"],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"In a bin status report, double-clicking on a bin that contains materials","options":["Produces a drilldown report showing details of the materials. ","Opens a screen that enables you to change which bin is shown on the report.","Produces information about the bin location.","Opens a screen where storage bin information can be configured.","Will not display any data."],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"Warehouse management is typically used","options":["By organizations that have small quantities of materials. ","By transportation companies.","By organizations that have either large quantities of materials or an expensive inventory.","By storage companies.","By organizations that demand better reporting for their inventory. "],"answerIndex":2},{"question":"A storage location is a key organizational level associated with inventory management. ","options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":"\t","options":["Moving materials between two storage locations within the same plant or different plants is known as storage location-to-storage location transfer. "],"answerIndex":1},{"question":"One-step procedure is possible only when the materials are in unrestricted use at the supplying location.","options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":1},{"question":null,"options":[],"answerIndex":0}]}